plugintogreenprofits.com 2010-12-29

# Plug into Green Profits- Privacy Policy .

**Plug Into Green Profits Privacy Policy**

Our company collects information in different ways from visitors and members who access the various parts of our services and the network of web sites accessible through our service.

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your address and telephone number will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Plug Into Green Profits.

**Registration**

Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our products or services including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the Services. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each member's account (such as for billing purposes).

This information may be shared with third parties, as stated herein, or in special circumstances.

However, in instances where our company and a partner jointly promote our Services, we may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address, and username of persons who subscribed to the services as a result of the joint promotion for the purpose of offering you other products and services. In this instance, personal information may not be used by the partner for any other purpose. We may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Members provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Members). As explained in more detail below, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on the Services. 

Also, with purchases, we supply our member's contact information, to our business partners, who then may contact the member by telephone after the member purchase. Sales proceeds are collected by that business partner company.  We also may supply other companies with contact information, for mail offers we believe would be of interest to our members, with or without compensation from those companies.  At times we may send an advertisement for a third party product, where we collect the sales proceeds, and forward the purchaser's information to that third party.

**Credit card details**

If you pay for anything on our site using a credit or debit card, we collect the personal information needed to complete the transaction. This information includes your name, card number, and other necessary information, all of which is clearly labeled on the form you use to submit payment. We use an unaffiliated, credit card processing company to process your payment. We transfer your payment information and you authorize us to do so, to this company solely for this purpose. The company does not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

**External Sites**

Plug Into Green Profits is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Plug Into Green Profits to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Plug Into Green Profits does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Plug Into Green Profits and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Plug Into Green Profits have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
